# **Christian Bakhit**

346-520-3898 | cbakhit1@jhu.edu www.linkedin.com/in/christianbakhit | bakhit.me

## **OBJECTIVE**

Dedicated Computer Science Undergraduate with two years of experience on a multitude of teams developing services for the greater community. Specialized in developing software for providing information to specialized groups. My long-term goal is twofold, to construct Artificial Intelligence to aid the average homeowner with menial tasks, and help design medical tools for hospital use.

#### **EDUCATION**

Johns Hopkins University

Baltimore, MD | 2020 - Current

Bachelor of Science

Expected 05/2024

Computer Science, Applied Math and Statistics Minor: Robotics, Computer-Integrated Surgery

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **DELINEO MODELING PROJECT**

Remote

Student Leader

Crosted the Amy Town simulation, a visual for COVID 10 lowers sing Unity, C# and Roset

January 2021 - Present

- Created the AnyTown simulation, a visual for COVID-19 leveraging Unity, C#, and React
- Manage a team of Computer Science students to implement Agile Project Management
- Presented Delineo in research conferences to obtain publicity and broaden public's knowledge of challenges facing epidemiology today
- Led design of the Delineo Website with the Fullstack team, implementing the MERN stack to enhance user experience of operating the Delineo simulation
- Facilitated communication with Microsoft Research and tested a COVID-19 dashboard on Azure Kubernetes

## SOUTHERN COPTIC DIOCESE PROJECT

Remote

Developer

June 2021 - November 2021

- Invented an application to present a database of information for minors using Flutter
- Developed a PDF viewer converts raw information into a user accessible format

#### SAINT MARY ARCHANGEL MICHEAL WEB DEVELOPER

Remote

Developer

June 2022 - Present

- Created and maintain a website using the React Framework, Firebase Database, and EmailJS
- On a team of two, deployed Firebase to store event information, pdfs, and miscellaneous other useful objects
- Provided new and consistent updates to design and functional aspects according to customer's specifications

# **SKILLS**

- English (Native), Arabic (Basic)
- Coding Languages: Java, Python, C#, C++, C, JavaScript, x86 64 Assembly
- Development Frameworks: Flutter, React
- Content Creation: Microsoft Office, Adobe Creative Suite, OBS, Android Studio, and Unity
- Project Methodologies: Agile, Waterfall

## **PROJECTS**

Jarvis Project

Personal Website

# PERSONAL PROJECT

Remote

Discord Server Bot (Python)

August 2021 - Present

- Devised bot takes in user input and responds appropriately. Utilized by students interested in Quiz Bowl competitions; reading a CSV of data and creates questions for students
- Developed a new design aims to leverage pre-existing infrastructure and serve users with information about large data breaches and website outages operating on Firebase Realtime database

### PERSONAL PROJECT

Remote

October 2021 - Present

- Speech AI takes in voice commands and responds with information such as weather and task creation
- Planned to work with home systems such as Ring and Philips Hue to control home systems

## PERSONAL PROJECT

Remote

March 2022 - Present

• Devised a personal website deploying React and JavaScript